杰森∶好吧,今天到此为止.
Jason: Alright, well, that's our session for today.
我我们将把这个办公室改造一下,因此下星期我们将在另一个地址了.
I'll be remodeling this office, so next week we'll be at another address, OK?
病人∶哦,一个真正的办公室,哈!
Patient: A real office, huh?
杰森∶这里就是一个真正的办公室拉佩克先生,我在这里工作.
Jason: This is a real office Mr.Lapepki, I do real work here.
杰森∶我不是说我们不要露梁平顶,但是,
Jason: Now, I'm not saying we have to have beamed ceilings,
我们要干净.
but let's not be afraid of spruce .
法兰克:我们为什么不先去看看你的办公室呢?
Frank: You know what, why don't we just go take a look at your office?
杰森∶好的.
Jason: Yes.
迈克∶开萝尔,我发现你好像突然对合同工感兴趣了?
Mike: Carol, do I detect a sudden interest in contracting?
开萝尔∶我只是看看带着电力工具,身材强壮,
Carol: Just because I look at a good-looking guy with a nice chest of
长的又帅的男人,并不意味着我要生他的小孩!
power tools, doesn't mean I'm ready to have his child!
保罗∶杰森西维尔!!
Paul: Jason Seaver!!
杰森∶保罗.
Jason: Paul.
保罗∶你个王八蛋!多久了?
Paul: You son of a gun!How long's it been?
杰森∶差不多一个星期.你上次还在我家吃过晚餐呢,记得吗?
Jason: About a week.You had dinner at my place, remember?
保罗∶哦!那我为什么要拥抱你?
Paul: Oh!Then why am I hugging you?
杰森∶我也不知道,
Jason: I don't know.
你每次见到我的时候都会这样做;你让我觉得很紧张.
You always do that when you see me; you're starting to get on my nerves.
保罗∶看过你的办公室了没有?
Paul: Have you seen your office?
杰森:还没有.
Jason: No.
保罗∶让我带你去.
Paul: Oh, let me show you.
杰森∶我真的很感谢你和菲尔能让我用这个办公室.
Jason: I really have to thank you and Phil for letting me use this office.
保罗∶嗨!拜托,
Paul: Hey jees, hey please, don't mention Phil, huh.
不要提菲尔.
He's off at a Zurich conference,
他跑到苏黎士去参加会议,而我却要留在这里看双倍的病人!
and I'm stuck here with a double patient load.
杰森∶至少你不因此而痛苦.
Jason: Oh, well, at least you're not bitter about it.
麦琪:他一定是开玩笑.希尔玛你看到预约单了么?
Maggie: He has got to be kidding.Thelma have you seen this assignment sheet?
希尔玛:没有.
Thelma: No.
麦琪∶希尔玛,是你打印的!
Maggie: Thelma, you typed it.
希尔玛∶是,但是,我可没有看;这样的话,我就不会介入进去.
Thelma: Well yeah, but I didn't read it.That way I don't get involved.
麦琪∶我想要做一次特刊,"为你们的狗狗的冬天做准备"."
Maggie: I'm supposed to do a feature entitled, "Winterizing your Dog."
比起给Esquire杂志写那些深刻的,
So rather than writing an insightful, respectable,
体面的,
journalistic piece for Esquire Magazine,
新闻事业的文章,我更愿意告诉人们怎样把防滑轮胎放在他们的指压按磨上."
I'll be showing people how to put snow tires on their Shiatsus.
希尔玛∶不错的压韵..
Thelma: Nice alliteration
麦琪∶今天我要表明我的立场.
Maggie: So this is the day, I take my stand.
麦琪的老板∶我没能好好的利用你的新闻才能.
Maggie's Boss: I have failed to make use of your journalistic talent!
我要负全部责任今天我要离开这里了.
I accept full responsibility!As of today, I'm out of here.
麦琪∶我不是说你应该辞职!
Maggie: Oh, well I didn't mean you have to quit.
麦琪的老板∶我不是辞职,是被开除了!
Maggie's Boss: I didn't quit, I'm fired.
麦琪∶你在开玩笑吧?
Maggie: You're kidding.
麦琪的老板:麦琪杂志社经理不喜欢我们的图像,因此我们雇用了一个媒介顾问顾问;他来,
Maggie's Boss: Station manager's unhappy with our image,
我就走.
so he hired a media consultant, he consulted, I'm gone.
麦琪∶但是这不公平.我们所有的人都要离开吗?
Maggie: But that is so unfair!Oh, what if we're all gone?
麦琪∶看来你今天过的不错!
Maggie: You certainly seem to have had a good day!
杰森∶太好了.不知道要怎么来描述,麦琪.
Jason: Good, doesn't begin to describe it, Maggie; I had a great day!
我今天真是太开心了!!我跟你说,我有一间神话般的办公室,
I had the most fabulous office, the people down there are terrific,
在那里工作的人都棒极了,今天,还有2个医生来咨询我关于专业上的事情.
and two doctors...count 'em...two doctors consulted me on their cases.
我从来都没有这么兴奋过!对了,你今天怎么样?
I have never been so excited.How was your day?
麦琪∶我的老板被开除了,接下来的可能就是我!
Maggie: My boss was fired, and I may be next.
保罗∶你愿不愿意接替菲尔这里?
Paul: How would you like to take over for Phil here?
杰森∶哦!
Jason: Well, it's a very unexpected offer!A very attractive offer!
是个很以外的建议.非常被谈到吸引力的建议.
Maybe we could do something finally about that free clinic idea,
可能我们可以实现我们在午餐的时候所讨论的开免费诊所的想法.
we talked about at lunch.
保罗∶绝对地!
Paul: Absolutely!
杰森:这就是我向往的工作环境.
Jason: This is exactly the kind of work situation I have always dreamed of.
保罗∶哦!,太妙了!
Paul: Oh, Jason, fantastic!!
杰森∶我很抱歉.
Jason: I can't do it.
保罗∶杰森,我保证不会再拥抱你.
Paul: Jason, I promise I won't hug you again.
杰森∶不是,保罗.我和麦琪有个约定.
Jason: No, I have a deal with Maggie;
我们说好,不管怎么样,
we have always believed that one of us should be there with the kids at
我们其中的一个都必须在家里看小孩.现在是她开始事业的时机了,不是我!
all times.It's her time for career opportunities, not mine.
杰森∶可是我不这样想.我觉得如果我不能确信工作的很开心的话...对了,
Jason: I feel that if Maggie's happy at her job, and by the way,
我还不知道我不能确信到底工作的开不开心呢.事实上可能马上就不是她的工作了,如果他们要开除她的话!
I'm not sure that Maggie is all that happy at her job!
哦,如果我不能确信被开除的话,它我不是就可以在外面工作了!!!
In fact it may not even be her job anymore if they decide who they're
不,不,我不是这个意思.
going to fire!Ho ho, wouldn't that be something if Maggie got canned!No!No!
杰森∶哦!亲爱的.
Jason: Oh hi honey.
吉∶亲爱的,你今天过的怎么样?
Maggie: Hi honey, how was your day?
杰森∶恩,既然你问了,
Jason: Well, to tell you since you asked,
那我有些事情想和你谈谈……
there was something kind of wanted to talk to...
麦琪∶今天绝对地,毫无疑问的,
Maggie: Mine was, absolutely with out a doubt,
是我一生中最辉煌,
the most fabulous day of my entire life!
最开心的一天!!他们不但绝对地同外面的解雇我.
Not only did they not fire me,
他们....你看看九新闻频道的核心人员名单.
you are looking at the core of channel nine's new news team!
从现在起,我们是一档新闻网络,
From now on we're a hard news network,
我是他们的一号新闻记者!
and I am their number one hard news reporter!
他们根本没想过要开除我,他们是想和我签一个为期7年的合约!!!
They don't want to fire me, they want to sign me to a seven year contract!!
法兰克:不,是真的.
Frank: No it's true...
开萝尔∶(在她的脑海里)上帝,多么迷人的眼睛!
Carol: (In her head) God, look at those eyes!
他在深呼吸,肯定是有话要跟我说:一定是的.
He's gonna take a breath, I've got to say something: I suspected that.
法兰克:如果你知道有多少女人认为我的店铺谈话很没劲的时候,你一定会很惊奇.
Frank: You'd be surprised how many women find my shop talk...boring.
开萝尔:笨蛋.(在她的脑海里)你说得太无聊了,不过你的店铺好像还不错.
Carol: The fools.(In her head) Your talk is boring, but your shop looks great.
本∶臭虫,放学后有聚会,我家;有激光,
Ben: Stinky, Party after school, my place; lasers, ladies, no parents.
小姐,没有父母.我打电话给你就是为了邀请你.
Of course you're invited, that's why I called you.
迈克∶本,本,
Mike: Benny, Benny, Benny,
本,要不要我对你的聚会给点提示?
let me give you some pointers on your little wing-ding here,alright?
本∶愿闻其详!
Ben: I'm all ears.
迈克∶如果……如果你要举行聚会,而且参加聚会的都是些吵吵闹闹的小家伙……如果!你不会希望爸妈知道这件事情吧……
Mike: Alright, now if...
if you are gonna have this party,
and if this is gonna be full of frisky little horn bowls...and if!
You do not want Mom and Dad finding out about this thing...
本∶迈克,别再说什么"如果"了!我一定要举办这是闹哄哄的聚会!
Ben: Mike, stop saying, if!I'm having the stinking party!
迈克∶本,给我点面子.
Mike: Come on Benny, give me some diability here.
迈克和本∶早上好爸爸!
Mike and Ben: Morning Dad!
杰森∶只有咖啡!今天轮到谁做早餐了?
Jason: Only coffee!Come on, whose turn to make breakfast?
迈克∶轮到开萝尔了.
Mike: Ah...Carol's.
杰森∶我要快点为我自己准备点东西吃.等你们成为家庭父母后,
Jason: Fine, fine, I'll whip something up myself.
你们就知道该怎么做了.
Comes with the territory when you're the parent who works at home.
麦琪∶早安.
Maggie: Good morning.
杰森∶早上好.
Jason: Morning.
麦琪∶回见.
Maggie: See you guys later.
迈克∶再见,妈妈.
Mike: See you, Mom.
杰森∶不吃早餐吗!
Jason: Not having breakfast!
麦琪∶哦,亲爱的,
Maggie: Oh honey, I can't stay.
我没时间了.狄克和史蒂夫说想和他们的记者新秀---我,
Dick and Steve said they wanted to talk to me first thing about some of
谈一些事情.喔,他们是这样称呼我的.
the changes they have in store for their new star reporter.
哦!亲爱的,
Ooh, that's what they called me.
我好像在做梦一样,真是难以置信!
Oh honey, I still can't believe all this is happening.
杰森∶我也无法相信.
Jason: Neither can I.
开萝尔∶法兰克……
Carol: Frank...
法兰克∶是.
Frank: Yeah.
开萝尔∶我可以摸摸你的钻头吗?
Carol: May I touch your drill?
杰森∶开萝尔!
Jason: Carol!
开萝尔∶爸爸,你怎么不敲门?
Carol: Dad, can't you knock?
杰森∶我要提醒你,
Jason: I just want you to know,
别以为我们不知道你今天没有做早餐.
that it did not go unnoticed that it was your turn to make breakfast, OK?
开萝尔∶今天该迈克做,不是吗?
Carol: But it was Mike's turn, remember?
杰森∶既然我来了这里,那我就不得不提醒你的是,法兰克这星期来我家是为了帮我改造我的办公室,仅此而已.这件事情,对我和我喜欢的事业来说,都意义重大.
Jason: Oh, as long as I'm here Carol, let me remind you that the reason
that Frank is here this week, and the only reason, is to remodel my office
OK?This is a job that is very important to me and a job that
I care about very much
法兰克∶西维尔医生,你没觉得我的工作有进步吗?
Frank: Doctor Seaver, isn't it coming along?
杰森∶谁会在乎?
Jason: Who cares?
麦琪∶早上好.
Maggie: Morning.
工人∶早上好.
Worker: Morning.
麦琪∶早上好!早上好!早上好!早上好!
Maggie: Morning.Morning!Morning.Morning.
希尔玛∶麦琪,你有完没完?
Thelma: Are you finished, Maggie?
麦琪∶既然我是新闻的主角,
Maggie: I just don't want people to change,
我就不想人员有任何的变化.
now that I'm the centre piece of the news.
希尔玛:他们说你一来就让你进去.
Thelma: Well they said to send you in as soon as you got here.
麦琪∶祝我好运.别自找麻烦了,我的运气已经够好了.
Maggie: Wish me luck.Oh, don't bother, I don't need anymore luck.
麦琪∶(在电视上.她的新闻旧作)谁说初恋情侣不会结婚.有时四条腿动物的爱情会显得更加的完美.
Maggie: (On TV.One of her old new pieces) Who says puppy love can't end
up in marriage.Sometimes love is lovelier with four feet on the ground
牧师:你让肯尼迪做你的合法妻子么?
Priest: (TV) Do you take poop eater Kennedy as your lawful wedded Shiatsu?
麦琪∶(电视)十九新闻频道麦琪马龙为您在长岛汪汪婚礼教堂报道.
Maggie: (TV) From the Woof Woof wedding chapel on Long Island,
this is Maggie Malone for Channel Nineteen News.
(她老板都在嘲笑这个节目)
(Her bosses are laughing at the show)
麦琪∶我会收拾好东西,马上离开.
Maggie: I'll just clean out my desk and be gone.
狄克∶麦琪,麦琪,坐下.
Dick: Maggie, Maggie, sit down.
史蒂夫∶这已经是过去的事情了,狄克对吗?
Steve: This is the past, right Dick?
狄克∶我的研究显示,新闻19频道所采取的方法,让观众远离了它.
Dick: My research says, News Nineteen's approach has alienated its viewers.
史蒂夫∶对.所以,
Steve: Yeah.Which is why,
现在狄克提出了一个行动计划,
Dick has come up with a campaign to let everybody know,
要让大家都知道,我们现在做的硬新闻.
we're a hard-news operation now.
狄克∶要在整个纽约市做广告.
Dick: Bill boards all over New York City.
麦琪∶哇.
Maggie: Wow.
蒂夫∶麦琪,不会再有狗狗婚礼.只有硬新闻,对吗,狄克?
Steve: No more dog weddings, Maggie.Hard news, right Dick?
狄克∶对,像健身者的屁股一样硬.
Dick: Hard as a body builders butt.
史蒂夫∶明天我们打算在你家拍摄此次行动的第一个宣传点.
Steve: Yeah, well we'll be shooting the first promo spot for the new campaign
tomorrow, your house.
麦琪∶我家!最好还是不要了.
Maggie: My house!Wouldn't it be better to do it..
狄克∶麦琪,你有没有看过丹拉瑟一边走在海滩上,
Dick: Maggie, did you see that spot with Dan Rather walking down the beach
一边思考新闻的录象?
musing about journalism?
麦琪∶没有.
Maggie: No I didn't...
狄克∶我们会请相同的导演来拍摄!
Dick: Well you're getting the director who shot that!
麦琪∶真的吗?
Maggie: Really?
史蒂夫∶麦琪,千真万确.
Steve: Maggie, you can put this in the bank.
十九频道要花大力气来做固体,硬新闻.
Channel Nineteen is going to be spending its resources on solid, hard news.
不会再报道小凸轮船员,
No more mini cam crews, and investigative stories,
调查新闻,也不会再有华而不实和无里头的东西.
no more flashy sets and hairdressers.
狄克∶听起来不错吧?
Dick: Sound good?
麦琪∶天啦,太棒了.
Maggie: Oh boy, it sure does.Oh, but I would still get to have a...
但是我还是得有个发型师,对吧?
hair person, right?
杰森∶……简而言之,
Jason: ...in direct, the core of Mr.
米歇尔先生的问题关键就在于他不敢对他的妻子说出他的真实感觉.哈,
Mitchell's problem is his inability to tell his wife, how he really feels.
这种病肯定是传染性的!
Ha, must be contagious!
杰森和凯文∶去掉最后一个字.
Jason and Kevin: Strike that last word!
凯文∶我会在午餐以前把这些笔记打印出来放在你的办公桌上.
Kevin: I'll have these notes, typed and on your desk before lunch.
杰森∶好的谢谢.
Jason: OK Kev, good.Thanks.
凯文∶你下一个病人安排在十一点,名叫泊若尔夫人.
Kevin: Your next patient isn't due until eleven...Mrs.Proll.
杰森∶哦!你能不能……
Jason: Oh, yes, well...err...could you...
凯文∶她的卷宗在你的手肘下.
Kevin: Her file's under your elbow.
杰森:凯文,我正在从一到十中选一个数字,你知道是几么?
Jason: I'm think of a number between one and ten, Kevin; do you know what it is?
凯文∶3.
Kevin: Three.
杰森∶难以置信的,3,
Jason: Amazing.Three, yeah; the number of days left before I say,
我想的就是3;我还有3天就要离开这个办公室了.
goodbye office.
保罗∶嗨! 杰森.
Paul: Hey Jase.
杰森∶你好保罗.
Jason: Hi Paul.
保罗∶我为我上次的行为向你道歉,因为我让你很难做.
Paul: I just got to apologise to you for giving you a hard time the other
我太自私,因为老实说我是多么的希望你能来这里工作.
day.I was being selfish,
但是,
because quite frankly I just wanted you to work here so bad.
既然你和麦琪有约定,你就应该遵守,
But hey listen, you made this deal with Maggie, and you should honour it, OK?
不是吗?真的很抱歉.
I'm sorry.
杰森∶不是吧?你不是来设法说服我留下来的吗?
Jason: That's it?You're not going to try to talk me into staying again?
保罗∶什么?
Paul: Sorry?
杰森∶我了解你保罗!
Jason: I know you Paul!
我知道你要设法把我和麦琪的约定打破.来吧,
I know you're gonna try and pick apart my deal with Maggie.
拿出你的杀手锏!
Go ahead, take your best shot!
保罗:不不不,你错了.坦白的说我尊重你的决定.
Paul: No, no, no, you're wrong, you're wrong.Frankly I respect your decision.
杰森∶不可能,不可能.我明白有很多理由可以来粉碎我们的约定,
Jason: No, no, there's a lot to pick apart, I know.
但是,你要知道,我们在5年前就有了这个约定.
And sure, we made the deal almost five years ago.
保罗∶不,不,不,你会发现你错了...
Paul: No, no, no, no, no, wait you're wrong...
杰森∶并且现在和以前不一样了,迈克,
Jason: And there is not the same need for a parent to be at home and
开萝尔和本都已经长大了,并且成熟了,根本就不用我们在家里看着他们.
Mike and Carol and Ben are all far older and more mature now, yes.
保罗∶你说的对,但是……
Paul: Well, that's true but..
杰森∶我知道,你要问克莉丝怎么办,在我们下面的大厅就有一个不错的看护中心;你可以用这些理由来攻击我呀,你为什么不呢?
Jason: And as for Chrissy, OK!I know, there's a great day-care centre down
the hall; throw that in my face, why don't you
保罗∶杰森,不是……
Paul: Jason, it's not...
杰森:保罗,
Jason: The point that you're missing here, Paul,
关键问题在于麦琪让我回家.即使没有理由,
is that Maggie expects me to be home.
有么?
Even if the reasons for it don't exist anymore...Well, they don't, do they?
保罗∶听着,我真的不是这样想的……
Paul: Listen, I'm not following this whole train of thought here...
杰森:好!好!
Jason: OK!OK!Paul, I will tell Maggie exactly how I feel!
保罗,我会告诉麦琪我怎么想的!不要管我.
Just get off my back.
杰森∶刚才我说到看护的时候,你在笑.
Jason: And hen I mention day care, you smile, OK.
是,因为你如果不那样做的话,我就是一个毫无生气的男人.
Yes, because if you do that other thing, I'm a dead man.
麦琪,开萝尔现在已经足够大了,
Maggie, Carol's obviously old enough to take care of herself now, and Mike,
可以照顾自己了,而迈克呢,我们已经尽了我们最大的努力了;对于本,
well hey, we've done all we can with him; and Ben, Ben he's so mature now,
你看他现在多么的成熟,不是吗?
isn't he?
本∶好了,现在是跳劲舞的时间.
Ben: Alright, now it's time for a little dirty dancing.
杰森∶本杰明赫伯特霍拉西尔汉弗莱西维尔!
Jason: Benjamin Hubert Horatio Humphrey Seaver!
本∶爸爸什么聚会?
Ben: Dad!What party?
杰森∶出去,快走,出去,出去,出去,都出去!你也在家里!
Jason: Out, go, out, out, out, out, everybody!Not you!You were home too!
开萝尔∶是,但是法兰克正在用动力工具.
Carol: Well yeah, but...Well Frank was using power tools.
杰森:我不想信……不能够相信你的孩子.我想到什么来着?
Jason: I can't believe...You kids can't be trusted.What was I thinking?
迈克∶嗨!
Mike: Hey Benny, here are those CD's that...
本,
that you absolutely cannot borrow for this illegal party that I knew
这些是为这次非法的乱七八糟的聚会借来的完全不合适的CD!
absolutely nothing about!
本∶走吧.
Ben: Come on.
臭虫∶本,是个很不错的聚会.
Stinky: This was a great party, Ben.
杰森∶走臭虫!
Jason: Go Stinky!
女孩∶你的名字是臭虫?真是人如其名!
Girl: Your name is Stinky?It fits!
本∶爸爸,让我解释迈克是怎样怂恿我这样做的.
Ben: Dad, let me explain how Mike got me into this.
杰森∶嗨!去楼上你的房间呆着,
Jason: Hey, I want you to go up to your room and don't you come down
等你能剃了再下来.
until you can shave.
本∶剃什么?
Ben: Shave what?
杰森∶我不管!我再不需要这些了!我真是难以相信..我居然把唯一一次能改变约定的砝码放在这些孩子身上!迈克,你去哪里?
Jason: I don't care!Now I sure don't need these anymore.I can't believe...My one chance to turn this whole deal thing around and I'm foolish enough to count on you kids to help!Mike, where are you going?
迈克∶我只是想把这些替你放进水中,爸爸.
Mike: We...well I was gonna put these in water for you, Dad.
杰森∶开萝尔,你到底在房间里干什么,
Jason: Carol, what was going on in there that you couldn't hear what was
听不见外面发生的事情吗?
happening out here?
开萝尔∶爸爸,我不喜欢你的隐含意思.
Carol: Dad, I don't like what you're implying.
杰森∶站住!
Jason: Stop!
开萝尔∶干嘛?
Carol: What?
杰森∶你的屁股上是什么 ?
Jason: What is on your backside?
开萝尔∶你认为这是法兰克的,爸爸!
Carol: You think these are Frank's, Dad!Dad they're mine!
爸爸!是我的!我刚才一直这样站着跟他说话.
Well, I was just talking to him and standing like this.
迈克∶开萝尔,爸爸只是担心你对那个伙计太着迷了.
Mike: God Carol, and Dad was worried you were hot for the guy.
杰森:也许我太担心法兰克了,说不清楚.
Jason: Maybe it's time I had a worried with Frank...Maybe more than a word.
开萝尔∶爸爸,别这样.
Carol: Dad, please!
杰森∶还有一件事就是你被开除了!
Jason: And another thing, you're fired!
麦琪∶克莉丝在楼上,已经可以走了.其他的孩子们呢?
Maggie: Chrissy's upstairs, ready to go.Where are the other kids?
杰森∶本刚才像子弹一样飞驰而过,
Jason: Well, Ben just blew through here like a shot,
开萝尔好像说要去公司吃草餐,迈克,
Carol mumbled something about breakfast at work, and Mike...
谁看见他了?
hey who's seen him?
麦琪∶我觉得不能怪他们.你昨天晚上对他们太粗暴了.
Maggie: I can't say I blame them.You were pretty rough on them last night.
杰森∶那你觉得我反应过头了?
Jason: Well, do you think I over-reacted?
麦琪∶我没说,反应过头.
Maggie: I didn't say, over-reacted.
杰森∶但是,你就是这样认为的,不是吗?
Jason: No, but you think that, don't you?Mmm?
麦琪∶杰森,冷静点;我们俩整个星期都在工作,
Maggie: Jason, just calm down; with both of us gone all week,
麻烦当然不可避免.
we were just asking for trouble.
杰森∶对,下个星期就会有一个家长留在家里了,不是吗?
Jason: Hey, they'll sure have a parent at home next week, won't they?
麦琪∶你觉得哪件比较好?
Maggie: So, which one do you think?
杰森∶参加什么?
Jason: For what?
麦琪∶杰森,我跟你说过,
Maggie: For the news promo they're shooting here after work; Jason,
他们下班后,会来我们家拍摄新闻宣传.
I told you about it.
杰森∶哦!那就蓝色那件.
Jason: Oh, yes, errm...blue.
麦琪∶蓝色这件?
Maggie: The blue one?
杰森∶恩.
Jason: Mmm.
麦琪∶你是从什么时候开始讨厌红色这件的?
Maggie: So how long have you hated the red one?
制作人∶好,我们开始!
Producer: OK, let's go, let's go.
麦琪∶神圣的牟利.
Maggie: Holy Moly.
跑步者∶在这里.
Runner: She's here.
史蒂夫∶麦琪,你在这儿.
Steve: Maggie, you're here.Let's get you into make-up and get rolling, kid!
快去化妆,拿上名单!我们现在是分秒必争.
We're paying golden time here.
狄克∶我现在需要丈夫和孩子们.
Dick: I need the husband and kids, now.
麦琪∶我以为你说过不会用我的家人.
Maggie: I thought you said you wouldn't be using my family.
狄克∶我没有.大家快点,让我们开始!
Dick: I'm not.People, let's hit the marks, come on!
麦琪∶这些人是谁?
Maggie: Who are these people?
狄克∶你的家人.
Dick: Your family.
杰森2∶唷!
Jason 2: Yo!
麦琪∶什么?
Maggie: What?
史蒂夫∶我们必须以责任为卖点,
Steve: We've got to sell some relatability here,
而一个家庭确实可以帮我们达到效果.
and a family really helps us do that.
麦琪∶那为什么不用我真正的家人 ?
Maggie: Well, why not use my real family?
史蒂夫∶我们的确讨论过,狄克对吗?
Steve: OK, we discussed that, right, Dick?
狄克∶没错.
Dick: We sure did.
史蒂夫∶结果,我们一致认为,
Steve: Consensus was, your real family was too...errm...
你的家人太……狄克,那是什么单词来着?
Dick, what's the word I'm looking for here?
狄克∶老的,史蒂夫,太老了.
Dick: Old, Steve!Too old.
制作人∶好了,我们开始,排在她后面!
Producer: OK, we are rolling and...queue her!
麦琪∶杰森,亲爱的,我帮你提提神,好吗?
Maggie: Jason, honey, can I freshen that up for you?
杰森2∶谢谢,麦琪.
Jason 2: Sure, Maggs.
麦琪∶我演不下去.
Maggie: I just can't do it.
狄克∶哦,为什么?
Dick: Oh, why?
麦琪:我不能叫他杰森.我是一个记者,我不能说谎.
Maggie: I can't call him Jason.I am a journalist, I can't say things that aren't true.
史蒂夫∶麦琪,我们都商量好了的.
Steve: Maggs, babe, I thought we went through all this.
狄克:麦琪,我是搞影像的,
Dick: Maggie, I am in the image business;
我不知道怎么做新闻.
now I would never tell you how to do a news story because I'm not a
但是,请让我工作.
news guy; but please, let me do my job here.
史蒂夫∶我们只是想通过这个宣传来让观众看到你是怎么样来做新闻的.你说什么?
Steve: Let's get some viewers watch you do the news, by making a great promo here.What do you say?
杰森∶嗨!我在游戏.
Jason2 : Hey, I'm game.
制作人∶还在念名单.
Producer: Still rolling.
麦琪∶宝贝儿.
Maggie: Honey.
杰森∶哇,这些是什么?
Jason: Wow, what's all this?
麦琪∶是宣传和……
Maggie: Well, this is the promo and...err...
杰森∶你是谁?
Jason: Who are you?
杰森2∶麦琪的先生.
Jason 2: Maggie's husband.
杰森2∶我才是麦琪的先生.
Jason: I'm Maggie's husband.
杰森2∶哦,你不是.是你的代理人打电话给你的吗?
Jason 2: Oh, no you're not.Did your agent call you?
迈克∶难以置信.我是一个演员,他们居然也不让我演我自己.
Mike: I can't believe it.I'm an actor and they won't even let me play me.
本∶扮演我的那个小家伙是个彻头彻尾的傻瓜.
Ben: The kid who's playing me is a full blown weenie.
开萝尔∶演我的女孩怎么样!
Carol: What about the girl they have playing me!
我是说她长的和我12岁的时候像吗?
I mean, does she look anything like I did when I was twelve?
迈克∶看不清楚,因为她是坐着的.
Mike: It's hard to tell, she was sitting down.
本;迈克和开萝尔∶嗨!爸爸;爸爸!!
Ben, Mike and Carol: Hey, Dad, Dad!!
杰森2∶嗨!嗨!嗨!嗨!嗨!我马上就来 !
Jason 2: Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I'm on a five!
本∶天啦,太奇怪了.
Ben: Boy, this is weird.
本;迈克和开萝尔∶嗨!爸爸,爸爸!!
Ben, Mike and Carol: Hey, Dad, Dad, Dad!!
杰森∶你们都给我安静点!
Jason: Just zip it, all of you!
迈克∶爸爸!
Mike: Dad, come on!
杰森∶如果你妈妈能够抓住这次事业上的机会的话,那不是很好吗?
Jason: Look, if your mom has a chance to take advantage here of a very
所以,我们不应该全力支持她吗?因此,
terrific professional opportunity, so don't we owe it to her to be
闭上你们的嘴巴,直到你妈妈完成愚蠢的垃圾的宣传!!
supportive; so just shut up, until she does this stupid stinking promo!!
迈克∶我更喜欢另一个"爸爸".
Mike: I like the other guy better.
希尔玛∶秘密地!!闲人免进.
Thelma: Behind closed doors!!Nobody's allowed in.
麦琪∶告诉我希尔玛,你觉得史蒂夫和狄克为人怎么样?
Maggie: Tell me Thelma, what do you think of Steve and Dick?
希尔玛∶我觉得我是为他们在工作.
Thelma: I think I work for them.
麦琪∶你也不相信这里的一些事情都在起变化了.
Maggie: So you don't believe things are gonna be any different around here.
希尔玛∶我当然相信.
Thelma: Of course I believe it.
麦琪∶我现在开始怀疑了.昨天拍摄的宣传一点也没有提到新闻,每当我问起的时候,他们总是说,相信我们,等到宣传出来就知道了,等到看到宣传就明白了.
Maggie: I'm starting to doubt it.That promo yesterday didn't mention a thing about news, and when I asked them what was going on, they said, trust us, wait until you see the promo, wait till you see the promo!
希尔玛∶想看宣传吗?别说是我给你的.
Thelma: Wanna see the promo?You didn't get it from me.
电视:新闻十九频道团队的核心人物---麦琪马龙,是一个忠实的新闻工作者!
TV :The heart of the new Channel Nineteen News Team, Maggie Malone.
一个有奉献精神的专业人员!一个领导楷模!
She's a committed journalist!A dedicated professional!A former cheerleader!
麦琪∶那不是我.
Maggie: That's not my body.
电视∶她也是跟大家一样的母亲!
TV: And she's a mom, just like you.Sure Maggs!
她不仅仅只报导新闻,
She doesn't just report the news, she lives it!
新闻就是她的生命!每个晚上新闻十九频道的麦琪马龙是一个完全值得信赖的人.
And you can count on this type of honesty every night on Channel Nineteen
(麦琪在电视上)我是新闻工作者,
News with Maggie Malone.(Maggie on TV) I am journalist,
我不会报道不真实的事件.
I just can't say things that aren't true.
麦琪∶老实说,他们所说的一切都是谎言.你相信吗?我宁愿报道狗狗婚礼,我也不要对着镜头说谎话,他们 跟我签7年的合约就是为了这个!
Maggie: Honestly, everything they showed us was a total lie.I mean, can you believe it?I mean I may have done dog weddings, but I have never lied on camera, and they expect me to sign up for seven years of this!
希尔玛∶是49个狗年.
Thelma: That would be forty nine dog years.
麦琪∶谢谢希尔玛.
Maggie: Thank you Thelma.
希尔玛∶当我发现的时候,却很难跟你说,因为,
Thelma: Well it's tough finding things to say,
你知道,如果我说了,他们肯定会解雇我的.
when the only things I could say could get me fired.
麦琪∶也许我应该去找他们,说点什么,
Maggie: Well maybe I'm gonna go and say a few things that could get me fired!
让他们解雇我.不行,我不能这样做.
Excuse me.I can't.
希尔玛∶我认为你能.你可以去做自由职业者,
Thelma: Oh, sure you can.
我经常听见你拒绝那些投稿的任务.
Take those free-lance writing assignments I always hear you turning down.
麦琪∶不,我很愿意,但是,我不能.
Maggie: No, I'd love to, but I can't.
希尔玛:你说你为了孩子要在家工作,这是机会.
Thelma: You said you wanted to be home for your baby, here's your chance.
麦琪∶不,不行.
Maggie: No, it's not.
希尔玛∶为什么不能?
Thelma: Why not?
麦琪∶因为我们不能2个人都在家工作.
Maggie: Because we can't afford to have both of us working at home.
希尔玛∶我不明白,杰森……
Thelma: Well I couldn't, Jason...
麦琪∶不,不.
Maggie: No.No, Jason and I have a deal and he loves having his practice
我和杰森有一个约定,他喜欢在家里工作,而我不能去添乱.
there and I just can't mess that up.
希尔玛∶你怎么知道他喜欢在家里工作?
Thelma: Well how do you know he loves working at home?
麦琪∶如果你了解我的丈夫,你就会明白,
Maggie: Because he just spent thousands of Dollars re-doing his office...
他肯花几千块来重新装修他的办公室,就意味着他喜欢在家里工作.
and if you know my husbands, you know that's love.
杰森∶哦,并不相同.
Jason: Oh, it's just not the same.
麦琪∶杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
杰森∶哦!亲爱的,我在这里.
Jason: Oh, in here honey.
麦琪∶哇,这个房间看起来很不错.
Maggie: Wow, this place looks great.
杰森∶当然.你今天工作怎么样?
Jason: Yep.So, how was work today?
麦琪∶你知道,那是工作.
Maggie: Oh, it was, you know...work.
我肯定你一定很开心在这里见病人.
I bet you're gonna be really happy seeing patients in here.
杰森∶开心,不能用开心来形容.
Jason: Happy...well...Happy isn't even the word.
麦琪∶我认为是这样.
Maggie: I thought so.
杰森和麦琪∶你知道……
Jason and Maggie: You know...
杰森∶你先说.
Jason: Go ahead.
麦琪∶哦,没什么,我只是在想.
Maggie: Oh, it was nothing really.I was just thinking.
杰森∶我也是,我……你怎么想?
Jason: Yeah, me too.I...errm...Well what were you thinking?
麦琪∶关于我们的约定.
Maggie: Oh, about our deal.
你回到家里来办公,因此我可以出去上班,
How you moved your practice home,
你对这个约定多么的满意.
so that I could go back to work and how great you've been about it.
杰森∶不,不是很满意.
Jason: Yeah, well, not that great.
麦琪∶你不喜欢在家里上班?
Maggie: You don't like working at home?
杰森∶不,不,我喜欢,我喜欢!
Jason: Well, no, no, I love it.I love it.
麦琪∶我也觉得是.我从来没有这么糟糕过!!
Maggie: Oh.I thought so.I've never been more miserable!!
(麦琪和杰森同时对对方说出自己的真实想法)
(Maggie and Jason shout out the truth to each other at the same time)
杰森∶我一点也不想在这个办公室工作!我想和菲尔在一起,那样,我就可以挣更多的钱,他们提供小孩看护,我还有一个秘书……
Jason: I don't wanna work in this office!I wanna be down there with Phil, I'd make more money, they have daycare, I even get a secretary...
麦琪∶哦!我讨厌我的工作!情况并没有任何的改观,事实上,情况变的越来越坏,他们居然我要在电视上说假话...
Maggie: Oh, I hate my job! It's not gonna be any better than before, in fact it's gonna be worse.They expect me to lie on camera...
杰森∶一个男秘书.他们要你在电视上说谎话?
Jason: ...a male secretary.They want you to lie on camera?
麦琪∶你可以永久地接管菲尔的生意吗?
Maggie: You could take over from Phil, permanently?
杰森∶你从来都没有说过你讨厌你的工作!
Jason: You never told me you hated your job!
麦琪∶那你为什么不告诉我你有机会拥有一间那样的办公室呢?
Maggie: Well, why didn't you tell me you had an offer like that?
杰森∶我本来要说的!
Jason: I wanted to honey!
但是,你对7年的合约那么的兴奋,
You were so excited about your seven year contract,
再加上我也不想违反我们的约定.
plus I didn't wanna violate our deal.
麦琪∶我也是.
Maggie: Well, I didn't either.
杰森∶你现在要了?
Jason: Well you do now?
麦琪∶我想在家里工作……我想再次从事写作……我想和克莉丝在一起.
Maggie: I wanna work at home...I wanna write again...I wanna be with Chrissy.
杰森:真的?
Jason: Really?
麦琪∶但是我怎么能让你放弃你的新办公室呢?
Maggie: But how can I ask you to give up your new office?
杰森∶我讨厌我的新办公室!我才不希罕我的办公室!
Jason: I hate my new office!I spit on my office!
麦琪:我还以为讨论这个会让我们很难受.
Maggie: Oh, I was willing to be miserable so as not to go back on our deal!
杰森∶宝贝儿,我也是!
Jason: Honey, so was I!
但是对你搭档来来说,却并不糟糕,婚姻到底是什么呢?
But, isn't being miserable for you partner, what marriage is all about?
麦琪∶哦!是我们的.
Maggie: Oh, it is for us.
杰森∶因此,我们有一个新约定了!
Jason: So...err...We have a new deal!
麦琪∶对.
Maggie: We do.
杰森∶呵呵,你有一个全新的办公室了.
Jason: And...err...you have a brand new office.
麦琪∶在这里?
Maggie: In here?
杰森∶当然.
Jason: Of course.
麦琪∶像这样?
Maggie: Errm...like this?
杰森∶对.
Jason: This.
麦琪∶我看书架乡里乡气的.
Maggie: Well I see...book cases, you know?More of a country look.
杰森∶麦琪,那是装修前.
Jason: Maggie, that's the way it was before.
麦琪∶是.
Maggie: Yeah.
杰森∶在花掉我5000美元前,麦琪.
Jason: Before I spent five thousand Dollars, Maggie.
麦琪∶对.
Maggie: Yeah.
杰森∶我想你可能不会都喜欢,说说看,你认为怎么样?
Jason: I don't think you've given this a fair shake.So what do you think now?
麦琪∶我只需要椅子!00:22:19,000
Maggie: The chair stays!